Guide to the Fred Rogers Fairchild Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Fred Rogers Fairchild papers
1901-1965
MS 202
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
10.25
(25 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, writings, notes, research files, and printed material which document Fred Rogers Fairchild's career as an economist, consultant, and author. Fairchild's work as a tax adviser to Connecticut, the territory of Hawaii, and Santo Domingo are represented, along with his studies of finance and taxation in the Northeastern states, the insurance and forestry industries, and post-World War I Europe. Fairchild's activities as a teacher of economics and a member of the Yale faculty are less fully illustrated. Many files concern Fairchild's activities after retirment from Yale, including his authorship of a textbook for high school students entitled Understanding Our Free Economy, and his interests in conservative causes.
Fairchild, Fred Rogers, 1877-1966
Conditions Governing Access
Gradebooks in Box 11 are restricted until January 1, 2021 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gifts of Fred R. Fairchild, 1956; Mrs. Fred R. Fairchild, 1966; and anonymous gift, 1969.
Scope and Contents
The Fred Rogers Fairchild Papers consist of correspondence, writings, notes, research files, and printed material which document Fairchild's career as an economist, consultant, and author. The papers document Fairchild's work as a tax adviser to the state of Connecticut, the territory of Hawaii, and Santo Domingo. Studies of finance and taxation in the Northeastern states, the insurance and forestry industries, and post World War I Europe are also included. Fairchild's activities as a teacher of economics and member of the Yale faculty are less fully illustrated. Many files concern Fairchild's activities after his retirement from Yale (1945), including his authorship of a textbook for high school students, Understanding Our Free Economy, and his interests in conservative causes.
Fred Fairchild and his wife donated the papers to the Yale University Library between 1956 and 1966. The gradebooks (1912-1945) in boxes 10 and 11 are an anonymous gift received in 1969. They are restricted for seventy-five years from the date of the student's graduation. The papers are arranged in files by topic or record type and they are listed alphabetically by folder title. For any particular topic the files may include correspondence, speeches, articles, interviews, press releases, printed matter, brochures, pamphlets, charts, notes, memoranda, and reports.
The most voluminous files are those relating to Fairchild's textbook, Understanding Our Free Economy. The book, which Fairchild first contemplated writing in the late 1940s, was to be directed to high school students with the intent to teach economic principles without socialistic bias. The files include correspondence with Fairchild's collaborator Thomas Shelly; with officials of the Foundation for Economic Education such as Richard Cornuelle, Dean Russell, and Leonard E. Read; and with E.M. Crane and Stanton Whitney at D. Van Nostrand Company. The files contain discussions of the book's reception among school book selection committees and proposals for revisions based on criticisms ranging from biased treatment of the Tennessee Valley Authority to accusations that the text advocated birth control. Topical files for J.W. Clise; Lucille Craine, who edited The Educational Reviewer; America's Future Inc.; and the Mel Gablers also relate to efforts to review and in some cases denounce textbooks intended for public school students.
Fairchild's interests in conservative causes are documented in the files for Americans for Constitutional Action, the Committee for Constitutional Government, Congress of Freedom, Inc., Intercollegiate Society for Individualists, National Committee for Economic Freedom, and National Committee to Preserve the Integrity of the Constitution. Fairchild's views on domestic and foreign policy issues are also included in correspondence with Connecticut Senator Thomas J. Dodd.
Biographical / Historical
Fred Rogers Fairchild was born in Crete, Nebraska, on August 5, 1877. He graduated from Doane College in 1898 and received a Ph.D. from Yale University in 1904, where he taught political economy and economics until his retirement in 1945. Fairchild was an expert in international finance and taxation and served as a consultant to business and to state, federal, and foreign governments. He also authored several textbooks on economics. Fairchild died in Bridgeport, Connecticut, on April 13, 1966.
Conservatism; Economics; Insurance -- Taxation -- Connecticut; Taxation -- Research; Textbooks -- Censorship; Connecticut -- Economic policy; Hawaii -- Economic conditions -- 1918-1959; New England -- Economic conditions; Economists; Educators; Cornuelle, Richard C., 1927-2011; Dodd, Thomas J. (Thomas Joseph), 1907-1971; Fairchild, Fred Rogers, 1877-1966; Read, Leonard E. (Leonard Edward), 1898-1983; Shelly, Thomas J.; Foundation for Economic Education, inc; Van Nostrand Reinhold Company; Yale University -- Faculty
- Inventory
  - Addresses (Box 1)
    General
    See also: box 6, folder 115
    See also: box 16, folder 224
    See also: box 25, folders 350-354
  - America's Future, 1957-1964, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - American Institute for Economic Research, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action, 1959-1964, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Analysis of federal budget, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Arbitration of dishwashers case, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Articles
    - "Economics of Utility Taxation,", 1942 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - "How to Stop Inflation,", 1943 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - "Our Currency Reform Problem,", 1907 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - The Shoreline Times, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - "What Can We Do About Government Spending?", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - "Why There Cannot Be Prosperity…", 1940 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Assets of corporations, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Biographical sketch of Thomas Adams, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Business Advisory Council, 1946-1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 51-54)
    See also: box 8, folders 132-133
    See also: box 12, folders 165-166
  - Business taxes, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cases
    - American Clock and Watch Makers, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Cement makers, 1921-1948, undated (Box 3, Folder 57-59)
    - Connecticut Bus Company fares
      - Fairchild statements, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - General correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 61-62)
      - Miscellanea, 1946-1954 (Box 3, Folder 63-64)
    - Connecticut Insurance tax laws, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      See also: box 20, folders 296-297
    - Connecticut insurance tax revision
      - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Documents, 1945, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 67-68)
      - Fairchild reports
        - Appendix, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 69)
        - General, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 70-71)
        - Summary, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - Notes, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 73)
      - Taylor, Edward I., 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Connecticut insurance taxation, 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Connecticut Unfair Sales Practices Act, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Definition of "Rent,", 1938-1945, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Guaranteed stock, 1944-1945, undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Metal lathe, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - New Hampshire Forest Tax laws
      - General correspondence, 1939-1944 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Proposed legislation, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 81-82)
    - New Hampshire tax laws, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Oppenheimer, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Railroad Holding Company
      - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Documents, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 86-87)
      - Other testimony, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Remington Arms renegotiation, 1942, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Rhode Island revenues, 1945, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Rhode Island Savings Bank, 1943-1947 (Box 5, Folder 91-95)
    - Rigid Steel Conduit Association
      - Correspondence, 1941-1949 (Box 6, Folder 96)
      - Documents, 1941-1944 (Box 6, Folder 97-98)
      - Memoranda relating to trial brief, 1941, undated (Box 6, Folder 99-100)
    - Tax-Free bonds
      - Correspondence, 1941-1955, undated (Box 6, Folder 101-102)
      - Documents, 1941-1943, undated (Box 6, Folder 103-106)
      - Documents relating to hearing before Senate Finance Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 107-108)
      - Documents relating to hearing before Ways and Means Committee, 1942-1943, undated (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Yale dishwashers arbitration
      See: box 2, folder 42
  - Chain store taxation, 1937-1940, undated (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Challenge, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Clise, J.W., 1959-1960, undated (Box 7, Folder 112-114)
  - Commencement address: Doane College, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Committee for Constitutional Government, 1940-1957 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Congress of Freedom, Inc., 1954-1957, undated (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Connecticut
    - Taxation, 1913, 1925, 1931, undated (Box 7, Folder 119-122)
    - Taxation of unincorporated business, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Connecticut Sales tax and tax revision, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Connecticut Savings Bank
    - Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Documents, 1959-1965, undated (Box 8, Folder 126-127)
  - Crain, Lucille C., 1949-1963 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Criticism of Bullock's Elements of Economics, undated (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Criticism of Thompson's Elementary Economics Revised, undated (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Criticism of Williamson's Introduction to Economics, undated (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Department of Commerce: Business Advisory Council, 1949-1965, undated (Box 8, Folder 132-133)
    See also: box 2, folders 51-54
  - Discussion of Paper, "Balancing the Budget,", 1933 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Dodd, Thomas J, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 135-136)
  - Economic texts (prior to Understanding Our Free Economy ), 1953-1954, undated (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - E.I.D. Du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Essays
    - "Appraisal of Value for Taxation Purposes,", undated (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - "Comments On the Federal Fiscal Situation,", 1939 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - "Federal Taxation of the Interest On State and Municipal Obligations,", 1942, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - "The Future of State and Local Taxation,", undated (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - "Harmonizing the Tax System,", undated (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - "The Impact of Federal Taxation on State Finances,", 1936 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - "Industry Must Have Capital,", 1937 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - "Public Finance Accounts,", undated (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - "Taxation and the Business Cycle,", undated (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - "Taxation versus the Roadside Billboard,", undated (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - "The United States Budget in the Past Decade,", 1937 (Box 9, Folder 149)
  - Fernald, Henry Barker: "Budget Suggestions,", 1939 (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - First National Bank and Trust Co. of New Haven, 1938-1955 (Box 9, Folder 151)
  - First New Haven National Bank, 1959-1965 (Box 9, Folder 152-154)
  - Fiscal systems of the United States, England, Germany, and France, undated (Box 9, Folder 155)
  - Forest taxation inquiry, 1939-1960 (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - Gradebooks
    - 1904-1914 (Box 10, Folder 157-161)
    - 1934-1945 (Box 11, Folder 162-164)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted until January 1, 2021 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  - The Havana Charter
    - Documents, 1949-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - General correspondence, 1949-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Hawaii (Box 12)
    See also: box 21, folders 302-305
    - Annual reports of the governor, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - Appraisal of taxation on enterprises for profit, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Attorney general's bill on individual income taxation, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - Corporate balance sheets, 1925-1928 (Box 12, Folder 170-171)
    - County auditors' reports, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 172)
    - Financial computation statistics, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 173)
    - General information, 1925-1930 (Box 12, Folder 174)
    - Governmental income and expenditures, 1926-1930 (Box 12, Folder 175-176)
    - Gross-net tax summary, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - Individual income taxation, 1925-1929 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Industrial figures, 1916-1929 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Information on agriculture, 1920-1930 (Box 13, Folder 180-181)
    - Legal interpretation of taxation on enterprises for profit, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Memoranda on inheritance taxation, undated (Box 13, Folder 183)
    - Memoranda on property taxation, 1920-1930 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - Population data, 1921, 1939, undated (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - Problems of taxation on enterprises for profits, undated (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Property tax rates, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - Reports of the treasurer, 1925-1929, undated (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - Summary of the Hawaiian taxaton system, 1901-1930 (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Survey of taxation on enterprises for profit, undated (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Taxation problems, undated (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Tax exemptions, 1925, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 192)
    - Tax laws, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 193)
    - Territorial income, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 194)
    - Waterhouse charts of taxation on enterprises for profit, undated (Box 14, Folder 195)
    - Wescott, Herbert E., 1927 (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - High school economics
    - General correspondence, 1948-1957, undated (Box 14, Folder 197-198)
    - Illiteracy in the schools, 1956-1964, undated (Box 14, Folder 199-200)
    - Royalty statements, 1952-1963 (Box 14, Folder 201)
  - Ho, Franklin Lien, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 202)
  - Hypothetical corporations, 1943-1947, undated (Box 14, Folder 203-204)
    See also: box 20, folder 298-299
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, 1925-1964, undated (Box 15, Folder 205-206)
  - Interviews
    - "Byrnes Sounds Warning On Inflation Danger,", 1943 (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - "Congress to Face Tax Dilemma at Opening of New Session,", 1944 (Box 15, Folder 208)
    - New Haven Evening Register, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 209)
    - "Ways and Means Committee Drops Pay-As-You-Go Tax Plan,", 1943 (Box 15, Folder 210)
    - Yale Daily News, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Lecture: "Forest Taxation,", 1909 (Box 15, Folder 212)
  - Liberty Amendment Committee of Connecticut
    See: box 17, folder 231
  - Lists of publications, 1938, undated (Box 15, Folder 213)
    See also: box 17, folder 239
  - Mansfield, George E., Jr.: "Mansfield's Lot Rule,", undated (Box 15, Folder 214)
  - Manuscripts awaiting publication, 1923-1951, undated (Box 15, Folder 215-217)
  - The Mel Gablers, 1962-1964, undated (Box 15, Folder 218-219)
  - Memoranda: motor vehicle taxation, 1930, undated (Box 15, Folder 220)
  - Miscellanea
    - Charts, 1945-1947, undated (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Documents, 1946-1947, undated (Box 16, Folder 222-223)
    - General, 1913-1957, undated (Box 16, Folder 224-228)
    - Reports and notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 229)
  - National Tax Association reports on motor vehicles, undated (Box 17, Folder 230)
  - National Committee for Economic Freedom, 1959-1965 (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - National Committee to Preserve the Integrity of the Constitution, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - Net income of corporations, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 233)
  - New England State Tax Officials Association, 1940-1965 (Box 17, Folder 234)
  - Notes on the federal budget, 1932-1937 (Box 17, Folder 235)
  - Presidential budget message, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 236)
  - Profits and the ability to pay wages, 1940-1946, undated (Box 17, Folder 237)
  - Programs of meetings addressed, 1921-1949, undated (Box 17, Folder 238)
  - Publications, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 239)
    See also: box 15, folder 213
  - Read, Leonard E., 1961-1965 (Box 17, Folder 240-242)
  - Recipes, undated (Box 17, Folder 243)
  - Remarks (Box 17)
    See also: box 8, folder 134
  - Reports
    - "A Study of the Dominican Tax System,", 1918 (Box 17, Folder 247)
    - "Federal Expenditures and Debt,", 1940 (Box 17, Folder 248)
    - "Financing Defense: Can Expenditures Be Reduced?", 1951 (Box 17, Folder 249)
    - "Notes on the Havana Charter,", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 250)
      See also: box 12, folder 165
    - "Statement Regarding the Taxation of Domestic Insurance Companies in Connecticut,", 1948 (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - "The Taxation of Personal Property of Corporations in Connecticut,", undated (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - "Taxation of Timberland,", 1931 (Box 18, Folder 253)
    - "Report of a Study of the Dominican Tax System with Recommendations,", 1918 (Box 18, Folder 254)
    - "Report of the Committee on Examinations of the Faculty of Yale College,", 1936 (Box 18, Folder 255)
    - "Report of the Committee on Uniformity and Reciprocity in State Taxing Legislation,", undated (Box 18, Folder 256)
    - Report of the Subcommittee on Taxation of the Advisory Committee of the Timber Conservation Board: Taxation of Timberlands, 1912, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 257)
    - "Report on the Administration of the Labor Law of the State of New York,", 1907 (Box 18, Folder 258)
    - "Report on the Finances of the State of Connecticut,", 1939 (Box 18, Folder 259)
  - Reviews
    - American Highway Policy by Charles Dearing, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 260)
    - 1933 Cumulative Supplement to Federal Income Taxation by J.J. Klein (Box 18, Folder 261)
    - Economic Stabilization in an Unbalanced World by A. Hansen, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 262)
    - The Federal Income Tax by Robert Murray-Haig, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 263)
    - Federal Income Taxation by J.J. Klein, 1929, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 264)
    - Federal Tax Handbook: Revenue Act of 1932 by R.H. Montgomery, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 265)
    - Federal Tax Practice Revised Edition by R.H. Montgomery, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 266)
    - The Financial Organization of Society by Harold G. Moulton, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 267)
    - Full Recovery or Stagnation by A.H. Hansen, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 268)
    - How to Pay For the War by John M. Keynes, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 269)
    - The New Capitalism by James D. Mooney, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 270)
    - Readings in Public Finance and Taxation by M.C. Mills and G. Starr, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 271)
    - The Taxation of Excess Profits in Great Britain by Robert Murray Haig, assisted by George Holmes, undated (Box 18, Folder 272)
    - TNT - These National Tax Eaters by T. Swann, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 273)
  - Rhode Island, 1937-1944 (Box 18, Folder 274-275)
    See also: box 14, folders 203-204
    See also: box 16, folder 222
  - Rhode Island state finances, 1944, undated (Box 18, Folder 276)
  - Savings deposits, 1940-1944, undated (Box 19, Folder 277)
  - Society of Sigma Xi and Scientific Research Society of America, 1953-1965 (Box 19, Folder 278-279)
  - Statement before Connecticut General Assembly Finance Committee at a hearing on taxation of domestic insurance companies, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 280)
  - Statement before Connecticut General Assembly Joint Committee on Finance at a hearing on the taxation of insurance companies, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 281)
  - Statement before the Financial Organization of the United States Congress, Committee on Federal Finance, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 282)
  - Statement before the United States House of Representatives, Ways and Means Committee
    - Hearings on Revenue Revision, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 283)
    - On taxation of the interest on state and local bonds, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 284)
  - Statement before United States Senate Committee on Finance, hearings on revenue Bill of 1941; Committee on Taxation of the Interest on State and Local Bonds, 1941, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 285)
  - Statement before United States Senate Finance Committee, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 286)
  - Statement before United States Senate Finance Committee on the "New Deal Tax Bill,", 1935 (Box 19, Folder 287)
  - Statement before the United States Treasury Department on behalf of the Connecticut Bankers Association, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 288)
  - State revenues, 1944-1947 (Box 19, Folder 289-291)
  - State taxes on savings banks, 1944-1946 (Box 19, Folder 292)
  - Study: Connecticut state finance, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Summary: "A True System of Governmental Accounting,", undated (Box 19, Folder 294)
  - Taxation of banks, 1936-1942 (Box 20, Folder 295)
  - Taxation of insurance companies, 1930-1941, undated (Box 20, Folder 296-297)
  - Taxes paid by corporations, 1943-1944, undated (Box 20, Folder 298-299)
  - Timber conservation board, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 300-301)
  - Typescript
    - The Tax System of the Territory of Hawaii, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 302-305)
  - Understanding Our Free Economy
    - Cornuelle, Richard, 1950-1956, undated (Box 21, Folder 306-307)
    - Corrections to be made, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 308)
    - Crane, Edward M., 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 309)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 21, Folder 310)
    - Promotion, 1951-1962, undated (Box 22, Folder 311-314)
    - Reception and acknowledgements, 1952-1954 (Box 22, Folder 315-316)
    - Revision
      - Correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 22, Folder 317-319)
      - Notes, 1955, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 320)
    - Second edition, 1949-1960 (Box 22, Folder 321-322)
    - Shelly, Thomas, 1949-1965 (Box 23, Folder 323-328)
      See also: box 24, folders 340-344
    - Teacher's guide, 1962, undated (Box 23, Folder 329-330)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority
      - General, 1949-1958 (Box 23, Folder 331-332)
      - Revision, undated (Box 23, Folder 333)
    - Third edition
      - Aucella, Joseph, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 334-335)
      - Crane, Edward M., 1960-1963 (Box 24, Folder 336)
      - Publicity and reviews, 1958-1964 (Box 24, Folder 337)
      - Revisions, 1959-1965 (Box 24, Folder 338-339)
      - Shelly, Thomas J., 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 340-344)
      - Whitney, Stanton, 1960-1965 (Box 24, Folder 345-346)
  - United Illuminating Company
    - Correspondence, 1943-1962, undated (Box 25, Folder 347)
    - Documents, 1948-1964, undated (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - United States federal finance, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  - Unpublished addresses, 1919, 1938-1948 (Box 25, Folder 350-354)
  - Volumes: Report upon the Public Debts of the Principal Countries, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Yale Co-op, 1953-1964 (Box 25, Folder 356)
  - Yale University: finances, 1942-1943 (Box 25, Folder 357)